Finding aid for the Aldous and Laura Huxley papers, 1925-2007 LSC.2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Aldous Huxley Papers
  - Novels, Essays and Articles
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, Unpublished Essays
      - Philosophy and Religion; Chesterton, Gilbert Keith, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Galton, Francis, Sir, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Huxley, Julian, Sir, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Haldane, J.B.S, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Beebe, William, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Bacon, Francis, Baron Verulam, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Hume, David, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Yeats, William Butler, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Shaw, George Bernard, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Carpenter, Edward, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Whitman, Walt, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Philosophy and Religion; Tzu, Chuang, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Arts; Coomaraswamy, Ananda Kentish, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Arts; Hsi, Kuo, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Arts; Kenko, Yoshida, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Arts; Vasari, Giorgio, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Arts; Pater, Walter, Horatio, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - Arts; Reynolds, Joshua, Sir, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Arts; Allston, Washington, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - Arts; Ruskin, John, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - Arts; Hawthorne, Nathaniel, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - Arts; Fry, Roger Eliot, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - Arts; Sickert, Walter Richard, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Arts; Viollet-Le-Duc, Eugene Emmanuel, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - Arts; Santayana, George, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - Literature in Particular; Dryden, John, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Literature in Particular; Eliot, T.S., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Literature in Particular; Taine, Hippolyte Adolphe, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Literature in Particular; Forster, Edward Morgan, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Literature in Particular; Wilson, Edmund, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Literature in Particular; Borgese, Giuseppe Antonio, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Literature in Particular; Dostoevsky, Fyodor, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Literature in Particular; Rozanov, Vasili Vasilievich, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Literature in Particular; Voltaire, Francois Marie Arouet de, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Literature in Particular; Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Literature in Particular; Hardenberg, Friedrich de, Baron, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Literature in Particular; Goethe, Henri Frederic Amiel, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Literature in Particular; Weil, Simone, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Literature in Particular; Whitman, Walt, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Literature in Particular; James, Henry, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Literature in Particular; Kipling, Rudyard, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Literature in Particular; Beerbohm, Max, Sir, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Literature in Particular; Sante Beuve, Charles Augustin, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Literature in Particular; Arnold, Matthew, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Literature in Particular; Bagehot, Walter, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Literature in Particular; Thompson, Francis, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Literature in Particular; Strachey, Lytton, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Literature in Particular; Hazlitt, William, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Literature in Particular; Woolf, Virginia, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Literature in Particular; Lessing, Gotthold Ephram, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Literature in Particular; De Qunicey, Thomas, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Literature in General; Blake, William, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Literature in General; Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Literature in General; Poincare, Jules Henri, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Literature in General; Lowes, John Livingston, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Literature in General; Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Literature in General; Wilde, Oscar, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Literature in General; Stevenson, R.L., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - Literature in General; Nietzsche, Friedrich Wilhelm, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - Literature in General; Jobert, Joseph, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - Literature in General; Grillparzer, Franz, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - Literature in General; Shenstone, William, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Literature in General; Wordsworth, William, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Literature in General; Butler, Samuel, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - Literature in General; Spitteler, Carl, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Literature in General; Baudelaire, Charles, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Literature in General; Shelley, Percy Bysshe, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Literature in General; Poe, Edgar Allan, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Literature in General; Bradley, Andrew Cecil, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Literature in General; Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Literature in General; Mill, John Stuart, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Literature in General; Aristotle, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Literature in General; Schlegel, August Wilhelm von, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Literature in General; Dickinson, Goldsworthy Lowes, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Literature in General; Fielding, Henry, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Literature in General; Woolf, Virginia, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Literature in General; Mann, Thomas, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Literature in General; Macaulay, Thomas Babington, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Literature in General; Gissing, George Robert, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Literature in General; Trollope, Anthony, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Eyeless in Gaza
      - Page proofs with corrections by Aldous Huxley, [1936] (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence; also mentions Text and Pretext, Perennial Philosophy, and Grey Eminence, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Final typescript for Harpers, chapters 1-13, with holograph corrections [1 of 3], no date (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Final typescript for Harpers, chapters 14-24, with holograph corrections [2 of 3], no date (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Final typescript for Harpers, chapters 25-53 [chapter 54 in published version], with holograph corrections [3 of 3], no date (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Frederick Catherwood Arch
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Genius and the Goddess
      - Reviews, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Grey Eminence
      - Setting copy with proofreader's notes; corrections by A.H. [?]; [1 of 2], 1941 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Setting copy with proofreader's notes; corrections by A.H. [?]; [2 of 2], 1941 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Page proof with author's corrections, holograph index manuscript with typed copy used by printer, 1941 Aug 27; oversize box (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Heaven and Hell
      - Typed drafts of several appendices to Heaven and Hell with holograph edits, no date (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Hopousia or the Sexual and Economic Foundations of
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - How to Educate a Man
      - Published Article, in Fortnight Magazine of the Pacific Coast, Part II, Jun 1955 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Human Potentialities
      - Off prints, 1960s (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Offprint, originally published in The Humanist Frame, no date (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - Offprint, originally published in The Humanist Frame, copy 2, no date (Box 64, Folder 26)
      - Offprint, originally published in The Humanist Frame, copy 3, no date (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Island
      - Typed draft with holograph corrections by Aldous Huxley, earliest extant manuscript, chapters 1-6 [1 of 3], no date (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Typed draft with holograph corrections by Aldous Huxley, earliest extant manuscript, chapters 9-12 [2 of 3], no date (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Typed draft with holograph corrections by Aldous Huxley, earliest extant manuscript, chapters 13-15 [3 of 3], no date (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Typed draft, early copy, chapters 1-6 [1 of 2], no date (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Typed draft, fair copy of original typescript; Chapter 9 (continuation until end), Chapter 10 (pp. 1-26), Chapter 11 (last part, pp. 33-40), Chapter 13 (second half), Chapter 14 (without heading from "she started the motor…"), Chapter 15 (pp. 24) [2 of 2], no date (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Typed draft with holograph corrections, earlier version of chapters 9-12, no date (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Typed draft with holograph corrections, early version of chapter 15 (incomplete), includes one holograph page for chapter 15 [?], no date (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Notepad with holograph notes and sketches, no date (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Final typescript for Chatto & Windus, Chapters 1-8 (Part I), pp. 1-215, with deletions and corrections by Aldous Huxley [1 of 2], no date (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Final typescript for Chatto & Windus, Chapters 9-15 (Part II), with deletions and corrections by Aldous Huxley [2 of 2], no date (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Final typescript for Chatto & Windus, first retyped manuscript, pp. 1-247; typescript by Mrs. R. Kloegman [1 of 2], no date (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Final typescript for Chatto & Windus, first retyped manuscript, pp. 248-530; typescript by Mrs. R. Kloegman [2 of 2], no date (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Page proofs from British edition, pp. 129-286 (end), 1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Jacket blurb by Aldous Huxley, typescript, 2 drafts, no date (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Typescript for Harpers; identical with English copy; Aldous Huxley's corrections transferred by a Chatto & Windus editor's hand in the American copy, with deleted full pages removed, chapters 1-6 [1 of 3], no date (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Typescript for Harpers; identical with English copy; Aldous Huxley's corrections transferred by a Chatto & Windus editor's hand in the American copy, with deleted full pages removed, chapters 7-11 [2 of 3], no date (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Typescript for Harpers; identical with English copy; Aldous Huxley's corrections transferred by a Chatto & Windus editor's hand in the American copy, with deleted full pages removed, chapters 12-15, with extra pages commisioned to be retyped [3 of 3], no date (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Harper edition, galley proofs, 1962 Jan 11 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Harper edition, galley proofs with holograph corrections by Aldous Huxley; includes holograph dedication "To Laura" by Aldous Huxley, 1961 Dec 13 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Harper edition, galley proofs before dedication "To Laura", uncorrected by Aldous Huxley, incomplete, no date (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Jacob's Hands
      - Mimeograph, 102 pages, co-authored by Christopher Isherwood, no date (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Jonah Christmas 1917
      - Photocopy, card catalog description, [1917] (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Literature and Modern Life
      - Typed copy, holograph edits, 1962; includes correspondence envelope addressed to Virginia Pfeiffer (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Literature and Science
      - Typed draft with corrections by Aldous Huxley, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Typed draft, intermediate, heavily corrected by Aldous Huxley, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Typed draft, fair copy, pages 1-100, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Typed draft, final, for Chatto & Windus, with introduction and translations, corrections by Aldous Huxley, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Page proofs, pages 65-99, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Typed script, used for setting, with revisions by Aldous Huxley, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Typed Draft, early, pages 1-40, [1963] (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Galley proof with holograph corrections by Aldous Huxley, 1963 Apr 1 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Page proofs, "probably not read by author", revised proof, 1963 May 1; 1963 Jun 11 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - M. Alderton Pink a Realist Looks at Democracy
      - Photocopy of preface by Aldous Huxley, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Man and Space
      - Typed Draft, with holograph edits, 18 pages, no date (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Typed Draft, with holograph edits. 18 pages, pencil note on page 1 "Great Ideas of Today, 1963 Britannica" (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Man on Earth
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Man's Most Dangerous Myth The Fallacy of Race
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Mescaline and the "Otherworld"
      - Photocopy, published in the proceedings of the round table on Lysergic Acid Diethylamide and mescaline in experimental psychiatry, American Psychiatric Association, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1955 May 12 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Moksha
      - Correspondence, articles and ephemera, with materials relating to Timothy Leary's imprisonment, 1971-1983 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Monday Evening Concerts
      - Typescript, clipping and pamphlet, 1955 Oct 17 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - New Directions for the American University
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Out of Time into Space
      - Typed draft [carbon copy], "Travel in USA Book," 5 pages, 27 Feb 1962 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Ozymandias the Utopia that Failed
      - Photocopy of published article, in Fortnight Magazine of the Pacific Coast Vol. 14-15, 27 Apr 1953 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Ozymandias, The Utopia That Failed
      - Article published in California Historical Quarterly, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Pacifism and Philosophy
      - Typed draft, 1935 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Pitch Lake A Story from Trinidad
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Politics of Ecology
      - Typed draft, with holograph edits, 21 pages, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Typed Draft, with holograph edits, Working title: "Democratic Institutions in the Context of Advancing Science and Technology," 15 pages, [1963] (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Typed Draft, with holograph edits, Working title: "Democratic Institutions in the Context of Advancing Science and Technology,", Feb 1963; with copy of published address An Ocassional Paper on the Free Society published by the Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Prefaces
      - Preface to book by Godel, Roger, 1957 Apr 9 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Preface to Mystics and Society by Ghose, Sisirkumar, 1963; includes letter to Aldous from the author (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Preface to Man on Earth by Charter, S.P.R.; typed drafts with holograph notes, no date (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Preface to work by Cutler, Max, Dr.; typed draft with holograph edits, no date (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Preface to work by Starkey, M.L.; typed draft with holograph notes, no date (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Preface to work by Balliot, Juliette; typed draft with holograph notes, no date (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Printing of Today: an illustrated survey of war ty
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Reflections on Tagore
      - Offprint, published in Indian Literature, vol. 4, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Report from Palermo
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Salt
      - Typed Draft, titled, with holograph edits, 7 pages, [published in Home in Garden], Mar 1963 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Science Technology and Beauty
      - Typed Draft, some holograph edits, 11 pages, no date (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Seven Meditations
      - Draft, Vedanta and the West, [1987 ?] (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Shakespeare and Religion
      - Typed Draft, holograph edits, 13 pages, [published in Show Magazine in 1964], [1963 ?] (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Typed Draft, with title page, two copies [second copy incomplete], some holograph edits, [1963 ?] (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Review, by S P R Charter, 4pages, 1 Aug 1963 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Page proofs, with some edits, 1963 Dec 5 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Article published in Show, The Magazine of the Arts; includes photocopy, 1964 Feb; oversize box (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Essay published in The Cornhill, no. 1040, summer, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Stars and The Man
      - Carbon copy and holograph note, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Republication, Air & Space Magazine, May 1988 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - T.H. Huxley Scientist, Humanist and Educator
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Texts and Pretexts
      - Page proofs for Chatto and Windus; with author's corrections, 1932; superceded by new proofs (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Page proofs for Chatto and Windus, 1932 Sep 23; revised proofs for setting (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - The Complete Etchings of Goya
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - The Conquest of Violence an Essay on War and Revolution
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - The Genius and the Goddess
      - Published in 3 Parts, Harper's Magazine, Apr 1955; May 1955; Jun 1955 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, Reviews, Aug-Sep 1955 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Typed script, dramatization by Aldous Huxley and Beth Wendel, no date (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Typed revisions, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - The Gospel of Sri Ramakrishna
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - The History of Tension
      - Photocopy, published in the annals of the New York Academy of Sciences, volume 67, 1957 May 19 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - The Manuscripts of D. H. Lawrence A Descriptive Ca
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - The New Frontiers in Beauty
      - Article published in Show, The Magazine of the Arts, 1963 Dec; oversize box (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - The Only Way to Write a Modern Poem about a Nightingale
      - Correspondence, from readers responding to article published in Harper's, Aug 1963; some letters refer to Aldous Huxley's essay Literature and Science (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - The Opportunities of a Night
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - The Politics of Ecology
      - Booklet, An Occasional Paper on the Free Society published by the Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - The Song of God Bhagavad-Gita
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - The Supreme Doctrine
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - They Still Draw Pictures
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - This Way to Paradise A Play in Three Acts
      - Photocopy of preface by Aldous Huxley, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Training for Peace
      - Photocopy of introduction by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Types of Prayer
      - Published in The Power of Prayer, Mananam, vol. 7, no. 4, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified
      - Typed Drafts, fragments of unidentified works, no date (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Unpainted Landscape
      - Typed Draft, some holograph edits, 14 pages, no date (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Typed Draft, some holograph edits, 14 pages, [very acidic paper], no date (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Utopias, Positive and Negative
      - Holograph notes and draft, typed drafts, [1963] (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Various
      - Clippings, reviews, articles relating to Ape and Essence, The Genius and the Goddess, Literature and Science, Giaconda Smile, and Island, 1962-1963; oversize box (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Voices
      - Typed draft with corrections by Aldous Huxley, act one, includes note from Peggy [Larson?], 1961 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Typed draft with corrections by Aldous Huxley, act two and three, includes note from Peggy [Larson?], 1961 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Typed draft with corrections by Aldous Huxley, separate draft, 1961 Nov 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Clipping, published story from the Atlantic Monthly, Volume 196, Number 1, 1955 Jul (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Adaptation, with correspondence, typescript with holograph corrections, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - What is Man?
      - Published Article, in Fortnight Magazine of the Pacific Coast, May 1955 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - White Corpuscles in Europe
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - You Are Not the Target
      - Photocopy of foreword by Aldous Huxley, no date (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Personal
    - Sketches of Aldous and Laura Huxley by Don Bachardy, 1962 Oct 11; oversize box (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Materials relating to Mariane Newton, 1950s-1960s (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Copy of typed draft titled "Three Questions Leo Tolstoi, originally in file titled Tolstoy Recipe, no date (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Bound copy of "The Menuhins A Personal Family Odyssey" by Lional Rolfe, features edits, no date (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - [Last writings on deathbed]
      - Holograph notes, includes original "LSD-Try it" note, 1963 Nov (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - [Note to Laura]
      - Note [to Laura] on acupuncture for the heart, with sketch of the hand, photocopy, no date (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - Fan letters, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Photocopies of Aldous Huxley's Correspondence from University of Houston, typed [?] copies of Aldous Huxley's early poetry, clippings, 1915-1965 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Horowitz, Michael, 9 Apr 1972; mentions Timothy Leary (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Gardner, [Reid ?] (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Archera, [Laura's Father], 1956-7 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Brooke, [Jocelyn ?], no date (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Burtt, [Edwin A. ?], 28 Jan 1963 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Dos Passos, John, 17 Oct 1963 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Fell, Vivian; photocopy of letter, 3 Mar 1955 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Gardner, Reid, 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Goddard, [?], 27 Jan 1962; mentions Laura Huxley's audio recordings "Rainbow Walk" and "Your Favorite Flower" (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Hubble, Grace, 16 Oct 1963 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Huxley, Laura; holograph letter and postcards, 1961-1963 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Huxley, Laura; photocopies of letters, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Huxley, Laura; photocopies of letters originally kept in binder [part 1 of 2], 1961 -1963; also contains photocopies of letters to Laura Huxley from Juliette Huxley (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Huxley, Laura; photocopies of letters originally kept in binder [part 2 of 2], 1961 -1963; also contains photocopies of letters to Laura Huxley from Juliette Huxley (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Huxley, Matthew, 1961-1963; mentions Aldous Huxley's novel Island (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Huxley, Trevenen, 2 Aug 1965; Letter from Trevenen Huxley to Mrs. Marguerite Nys (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Kiely, William F., M.D., 19 Mar 1962; included is note to Aldous Huxley from Laura Huxley (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Kroger, William S., 30 Dec 1962 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - [Lindlan ?], Maris, 26 Jun 1962 (Box 48, Folder 17)